(Bernadette:)...for a man with a closet full
of magic tricks at his mother's house.
(Howard:)First of all, they're not tricks.
They're illusions.
(Howard:)Secondly, when we get married,
they're all going up in the attic...
(Howard:)...so you can have that closet
for clothes.
(Bernadette:)Why would I keep clothes
at your mother's house?
(Howard:)Well, don't think of it that way.
(Howard:)Once we move in, it'll be our house.
(Bernadette:)Is she moving out?
(Howard:)Why would she move out?
It's her house.
(Bernadette:)Hang on. You seriously think
I'm gonna live with your mother?
(Sheldon:)Howard, I think I can help here.
(Sheldon:)Yes, Bernadette,
that's exactly what he thinks.
(Howard:)Why not?
It's a great house, plenty of room.
(Howard:)If we have kids, Mom's there to help.
When she tells "The Three Little Pigs"...
(Howard:)...she actually has hair
on her chinny chin chin.
(Bernadette:)I'm not gonna live with your mother.
Not now, not ever.
(Howard:)Wow, someone obviously has
some mommy issues.
(Bernadette:)Raj, take me home.